osiaffiliate.com 2008-06-09

# ebusiness software | Privacy

Omnistar Interactive has created this privacy statement to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. This statement sets forth our information gathering and dissemination practices for all sites in the Omnistar Interactive family of sites. 

**What We Collect and Where**  
Our sites use several different forms that our customers can use to request information, products, and services. From these forms, we collect the following information:

  * Visitors' contact information 

  * Financial information 

  * IP addresses 

**How Secure is the Information We Collect?**  
Omnistar makes every effort to follow industry standard security measures to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. 

**What Do We Use This Information For?**

**Contact Information**  
We use your contact information to send you information about our company and to get in touch with you when necessary. We also use the information we collect to improve the content of our Web site. Our site allows you to opt out of receiving communications from us. You will be given this choice at the points where we request your information. If you do not wish to receive future marketing mailings, please un-subscribe.

**Release of Personal Information in Extraordinary Circumstances**  
Except as provided for in this Privacy Policy, Service Provider will never share Customers' personal information with third parties without Customers' express permission unless extraordinary circumstances apply. With respect to the release of personal information, extraordinary circumstances may exist when the disclosure of such information is legally required or requested by a governmental entity, or when Service Provider, acting in good faith, believes that the disclosure of such information is necessary to conform to legal requirements or comply with legal process, protect the rights of Service Provider, prevent a crime or protect national security, or protect the personal safety of its Customers or the public.

**Privacy Policy Changes**   
If we decide to change our Privacy Policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy, our Web site, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Policy, we will notify you via this page.

**We value your opinions and feedback**. If you have comments or questions about our Privacy Policy, please email [_support@omnistaretools.com_](mailto:support@omnistaretools.com).
